Guide to the Clifton R. Merritt Papers 1935-2008
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana-Missoula
- Motion Picture Films, Series IX; 14 16mm films
  - Fishing Trip, ca. 1972; Shot of highway sign for Swan Lake, Polson, and Missoula. Various shots of Flathead Lake, men fishing, women on beach, men in canoe, children fishing and playing, boating, and the camp.; 16 mm; Color, 210 ft, No Sound (Reel 14)